Here we are, all over again.
You know, it's always around this time of year
that I start to feel a heightened sense of anxiety.
The attacks, the attacks start to get stronger.
People start feeling really bold, you know,
about just really, really just standing their ground.
Something is wrong with me for loving candy corn.
That girl be acting.
Y'all see me acting?
Ooh, she gagged.
While I have you, I want to remind you
that every second Wednesday of the month,
you can catch me at Comedy in Harlem
doing my thing, combining humor with energy work
and music and creating a safe space
for all of us to level this vibration up.
Tickets are available right now at the link in bio
and at comedyinharlem.com.
See you there on Wednesday,
August 12th at 7.30 p.m.
Bring me some candy corn.